<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chen Shao | Tianqi Jiang&#39;s curriculum vitae</title>
    <link>/authors/chen-shao/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/chen-shao/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Chen Shao</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>img/map[gravatar:%!s(bool=false) shape:circle]</url>
      <title>Chen Shao</title>
      <link>/authors/chen-shao/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emission reduction process for dechlorinating flue-gas desulfurization gypsum and reducing wastewater effluents: Application prospects from laboratory-scale studies</title>
      <link>/publication/journal-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/journal-article/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;　The treatment of flue-gas desulfurization (FGD) gypsum, a common solid waste material that is often affected by chloride ions, typically occupies large amounts of land, causes resource waste, and results in environmental pollution. An emission reduction process involving the dechlorination of FGD gypsum and reducing its emissions has been proposed to solve these problems. Laboratory experiments were conducted to verify the feasibility of the emission reduction process and study any differences from the conventional process. The test results indicated that the average dechlorination rate of the emission reduction process was 80.4%, which is equivalent to 97.5% of the conventional process. The average dechlorination wastewater volume of the emission reduction process was 0.22 L, which is equivalent to 4.9% of the conventional process. The results show that the emission reduction process can effectively reduce the chlorine content of FGD gypsum and its related wastewater discharge. This novel gypsum dechlorination process effectively reduces the chlorine content of FGD gypsum and related wastewater. In addition, the emission reduction process can lead to greater recovery of renewable resources and can result in a cleaner energy conversion process. This process is an alternative method for recovering residues and resources without secondary pollution. Therefore, if this technology is integrated into existing FGD facilities, costly chemical processes could be replaced by those that recover a renewable resource and incorporate a clean energy conversion process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　Concrete; Back-filling; Dechlorination; Emission reduction process; Flue-gas desulfurization gypsum; Wastewater, Fly-ash; Soil Properties&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
